So, the book is like, you read the book, you don't want to watch the movie.
I like the movie.
But when you read the book, you don't want to, you say, why they didn't do that in the movie?
And at the end, they put, they put like, uhh, como una inyección.
El podia escoger una inyección o una pastilla, tomarse una pastilla.
O salir para la calle, y bajarse con todo el mundo.
It was like a murder.
For them, it was like a murderer.
A murder?
Como un asesino.
Porque ya ellos tenian su comunidad.
Yeah.
They were like living like no...
Yeah, but they're crazy, they killed people.
No, they don't kill people.
They don't kill...
Ellos no mataron a su propia gente.
Ellos mataron a la gente como nosotros.
Pero exactly, that's like, that's killing people.
Because there were still some survivors left.
You know, but I don't know.
I know, they adapted.
Yeah.
Adaptaron a la vida de ellos.
I want to see it.
You want to see the first one?
The one that came on the movie?
Yeah.
On the movie theater?
I want to buy it.
The special edition is the one that comes with the...
Yeah.
It's like 20-something, 20-something bucks.
I want to see it.
Cool.
And in the book, he drinks the pills.
It's like, you know...
Se enfoca, como que se va llendo así no.
But in the book, there is a girl that betrayed him.
Que se hace pasar por humano, pero es de, de los demás tipos.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
That's the cool part.
That they don't show you in the movie.
Yeah, but they can't do that in the movie.
Why?
Because all the monsters look like...
They look like zombies.
Yeah.
And all the people look like normal people.
So, like, there's no way...
Well, remember, he had that girl on the bed?
That one.
That one. Se estaba curando.
In the ending it showed you the girl is like curing, is like helping.
Cuando se la va a entregar, le da un shot, y se convierte de nuevo.
You saw that?
The girl was breathing, like, a lot.
Yeah.
And then, en el final, estaba como mas passiva,
El tipo le da un shot, de otra,
No se que, lo que tenia el.
Y se pone mostró de nuevo.
Yeah.
So, he closes the door and thats it.
Look at that.
Look at that, brother.
Oh, my God, bro.
So, none of the endings is, like, relative to, to the movie.
To the book.
Right.
Yeah, I heard, like, there's a different...
There's different versions of the movie and the book.
There's an old movie.
Like, I Am Legend?
It's a remake.
Yeah, it's like...
They got like three movies.
Yeah.
But I don't know where they can do the movie by the book.
They already got the book.
Sometimes they got to change stuff, you know?
Sometimes they can't all be the same.
So, you have to work at 12?
Yeah.
Why so early?
Because they got a lot of clothes and...
12 to what?
To 6.
My regular...
I start at 12 and...
So, you do more hours?
Yeah.
But just for today.
More hours for you, bro.
Yeah.
I wish they gave me 12 every day.
John was telling me something about the show called
Que pasa USA?
Are you seeing it?
Which one?
Que pasa USA?
I don't know.
Bro, el programa es en el canal 2
que la gente es una familia y hablan inglés y español.
Aha, si.
You seen it, show?
Yeah, but I want to see it more,
but I don't know what channel it is.
Es un programa viejo.
Yeah, I know.
It's like Cubans or something like that.
Yeah, they speak Spanish and English.
Is it in channel 2?
I don't know.
They give it like in the morning and like in the afternoon.
I check it out online.
Yeah, check it out.
Que pasa USA?
He was telling me que quería grabar programas.
Who?
This guy?
He talk Spanish?
A little bit, he does.
Yo, have you seen the heroes yet?
I'm going to see it today.
When I go home now,
I'm going to go see like 2 episodes.
How was it?
The chat tonight, bro.
It's awesome.
You saw it?
Yeah.
You saw it last night?
No, no.
I just got stuck on the chat tonight.
I got to say 10 and 11.
11?
It's the last one.
I don't know.
That's why.
The 11 is when they got the strike thing.
Striking.
Yeah.
I think that it just ended right there.
It ended because of the strike.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking,
but there is like 7 pictures.
You know the 7 pictures that they found?
And they just got like 4 of them, right?
4 of them.
What do you mean pictures?
Isamendez, the painter?
Oh, yeah.
He painted 7 pictures, Ante de Maurizio.
They found the pictures.
One of the pictures is the guy of the clerk.
You saw the part?
The guy of the what?
That he's like, como, muerto.
Que se ve como muerto, con un tiro in the glass.
Yeah, yeah.
That's one.
The other one is this.
I don't like that one.
Which one?
I don't want him to die.
No, they're gonna show you at the end of the chapter 9,
you're gonna see.
Damn, it can't happen.
Damn, I gotta see it, bro.
You gotta see it because it happens something that you see.
You see something.
You wanna tell me?
I wanna tell you, but I don't wanna tell you.
Yeah, yeah, don't tell me. Dont tell me.
You're gonna see something that they can do with them,
with their abilities.
I mean, with that special ability that they can put to another people.
You know, you're gonna see what's happening at the chapter 9.
They're gonna say, wow, what's happening here?
Wow.
I don't know, bro.
I used to come to this movie theater so much.
Huh?
Is this the movies you come to?
No.
Yeah, Dolphin.
I go to the Dolphin.
Because this one closed like earlier.
Yeah, it closed earlier.
Open?
Shutter?
Shutter, yeah.
Yeah, I saw the failure yesterday.
Yeah, I wanna see it.
It looks like it works. He works.
That movie works.
This guy, I remember the face.
But it looks like one Spanish guy working on that movie.
You know who's in that movie?
Mando.
You know Mando?
Oh, yeah.
Mando from Heroes.
I thought that was a Spanish guy, but it was Mando, the one that saw it.
Yeah.
I saw it, but you know like, el perfil.
Thats Mando.
But they didn't put it again.
So, you know, I was like, that's an Mando thing.
Yeah.
El es modelo creo.
Really?
Yeah.
I go to Wikipedia, the Cyclopedia online.
Yeah, Wikipedia.
Yeah.
Y pon el, the profile there.
Sale el,
Sale en Meiga.
El del chamaquito
Sale en dio.
Sale en
En que mas sale/
Sale en Nathan?
Nathan Pagerle.
Sale en Peter, también.
Sale en tipo este, el Indu.
They're all models?
No.
Oh.
That guy Mando. El indu no me acuerda que era, el es de chicago.
Syrash?
Syrash, yeah.
Mohender?
And you're going to see what happened with Syrash, too.
Yeah, you're going to say, I can't have him.
I don't know how he changed.
You know, my point, he changed.
The cheerleader pisses me off, bro.
Yeah.
She pisses me off.
She made that up at the same time.
Yeah, everything is the same.
I want to help people, I want to help people, I want to help
people, what?
Get out!
Yeah, exactly.
I don't want to, yeah.
And you saw, you saw her boyfriend?
Yeah, and he pisses me off even more.
Yeah.
Stupid Superman guy, he thinks he's Superman and shit.
I can fly, you can hear, I can fly, you can hear, that's it.
Yeah.
The only interesting part that they do is when this
girl, the cheerleader, this girl, he's the other part,
El la deja caer, y Ella se cae. You didnt see that part?
Oh, when they were on the mountain?
Wait, what part was it?
No, no, no.
Ahi una parte where the cheerleader esta tomando.
You didn't see the part?
Well, is that episode six or seven?
I don't really remember.
I haven't seen six.
I'm going to see six today.
Ahi una parte que ella esta tomando. Y ellos quieren como asustarla
Como algo esta cambiando.
Y entonces, ellos planean algo, y el se pone una mascara.
Y El la sube, y la deja caer, y parece un fantasma.
Tu sabes, como para asustarla.
Oh, I see.
Y el le dice, viene la policía, y Claire.
Y Claire esta normal y después viene el muchacho para hacerla como que
Como estaba loca.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, I see.
That's the only part that, you know, like it's like funny.
Pero I say, you know, en la primera parte hacia mas.
Yeah, and Claire is not doing anything.
She's just complaining all the time.
Yeah, en la primera parte estaba mal.
She's always mad at her father.
And her father's just trying to protect her.
And when it pisses me off, she doesn't listen to him. You know.
That's what happened.
The thing is in the chapter nine.
Doesn't listen to him.
No.
Um.
Hero sees the hotel, the father.
He sees?
Yeah.
Does hero come back?
I want him to leave the past already.
Yeah, me too.
I want him to come back.
Is everything on the same?
That's what I'm telling you.
Everything in the same role.
Like heroes over there, he's over there on the 60.
On the 15, 40 or something?
Yeah, something like that.
And they don't do anything.
With Kenzie, but he's coming back.
Did he come back already?
Yeah, on chapter eight, he comes back.
At the end of the chapter eight, I think, yeah.
I like what's going on with Peter, though.
I like, well, I'm interested in like the Peter story,
like what's going on with Peter.
Because like he saw the picture.
He's like, oh, I got to go.
And then the girl's father got killed.
But the girl's hot, by the way.
On this season, yeah, the only one that I want to know
is, you know, last season, it was Hero, the one that I wanted.
I want to be like, you know, like I want to be seen.
Because it's the funny stuff.
Pero en esta no esta haciendo nada.
So yeah, that's what you're saying.
Maybe next season or something.
Peter is the only one that you're interested in about.
Peter and Nathan.
Porque en la, en la...
Nathan?
Oh, yeah.
Cuando ellos vienen de pasado, cuando ellos vienen en la parte de
Four months ago.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Nomas te voy a decir esto
Four months ago, you saw Nathan, tu viste como la cara nomas.
Yeah.
Cuando el sube para alla arriba, el empieza a quemar.
Y luego después tu quieres saber como fue que se curo completo.
Porque después de eso el esta curado.
Yeah.
And they show you?
Yeah, they show you what happened.
Yeah.
On Saturday night.
That's what...
And then Nicky, Nicky is in like the hospital that...
Nicky is always...
She doesn't have a stupid one.
Yeah.
And the black guy too.
What black guy?
The husband.
He's dead.
No.
The else dead.
No, you got to see that part too.
Oh, really?
But he's dead because Linderman.
He's dead because Linderman killed him?
No, no.
And later on, on the chapter night, they're going to show you who killed him.
He's dead.
But Linderman is not the one that killed him.
They go to a hospital and lo curan.
Oh, and then someone kills him?
Later on, having something with Jessica, that he goes where Jessica is.
And...
You know who I like too?
I like...
Look, I like Peter Petralli, hero this season, not so much.
But I like hero.
And I like the cop.
I don't like the cop.
I like the cop.
I like the cop with Suresh, taking care of the little girl, trying to figure out like...
They put the cop and Suresh a lot, but they don't do anything.
They just talk.
Well, yeah.
Don't you remember?
I like to go find the cop's father.
And the cop, the father, like, he's the one that, like, with the power.
Yeah.
That he put them, he put them both fighting against each other.
Remember?
Yeah.
And they didn't know.
Because they can put something on the head of the people.
Yeah.
They can control the people.
Do you like the girl, the Honduran girl, with the brother?
That was Tyler?
Kind of.
You like that?
Yeah.
I like Tyler.
He's bad.
You know, but...
They haven't put Tyler, like, later on.
They haven't put any other shotters.
Really?
No.
That's the thing that I was talking about.
I heard, I heard with chapter 11, has a lot to do with Tyler.
Like, yeah?
He's in it a lot.
What I was telling you, that they just put everything in one chapter.
Chapter nine is everything.
If you see, like, six, seven, eight, that's it.
You don't have to see the rest of the chapters.
Because everything is the same thing.
You just got to see six, seven, eight, and nine.
That's it.
With those four chapters, you're going to see everything what happened on the rest of the chapters.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
What?
Did they show you the future again?
Because chapter nine is everything.
Chapter nine is what happened...
Four months before, like, after the explosion.
Yeah.
You know, you got to see, you got to see, like, two or three chapters before chapter nine,
because you got to see what happened with Peter, how did he get there,
what happened with the girl that just got the flame and everything.
Yeah.
We'll see.
Hey, have you heard about that raise that we're getting in August?
The $1.20?
No.
Supposedly with the new contract I went through.
Oh, yeah, but...
Yeah, yeah.
We're getting a raise on the 20th.
What time you got there?
11.34.
I heard about it last year, that they're going to change company.
Yeah, supposedly we're getting a $1.20 raise in August.
They're going to change union and stuff, and they're going to raise twice a year.
I hope so.
Yeah.
Yeah, that'd be awesome.
Do you like...
Do you like Everett?
Sometimes.
Cai bien pesado a lot
Most of the time, pesado, but sometimes it could be cool.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
He gets a little pesado sometimes.
Sometimes.
Hey, they're still putting a jumper there.
Yeah?
You didn't see it?
No.
It's good.
Yeah.
Which one is the other one that is the bottom?
Step up, too.
Have you seen that one?
You know which one is good?
Vantage Point.
Oh, yeah.
I saw the trailer though.
Yeah.
Awesome.
You see the movie in the point of views of everyone.
Yeah.
They show you the movie in the point of view of the cop.
And then they go all the way back, rewind.
So everything happened, but in the point of view of a guy filming with a camera.
Like, it's awesome.
But everything is happening with the cameras, or everything happened with the point of view
of...
Point of view, normal.
Yeah.
But I saw...
Those are different people.
Yo vi que, This guy had a camera, like a periodist.
Yeah.
He had a camera.
Le quitaban la cámara
Y le chequeaban un video they took.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But what do you mean with the point of view of the cop?
Ellos te hacen que tu diga lo que paso.
No, no.
Like, they show the beginning of the movie, and then the big explosion happens.
No.
The president gets shot, and then a big explosion happens.
And then, like, they rewind.
And then, like, at Guardia, the security of the bodyguard of the...
The president.
Of the president, they show, like, everything that happened from his point of view, like,
what he was seeing.
And then from another person.
You have to see it.
It's good.
And then at the end, they put you the point of view of the killer.
You saw it already?
Yeah.
No, don't tell me.
Don't tell me.
No, watch.
I wanna see. You saw this one?
No.
10,000 BC, I want to see.
What?
Do you know what I don't like about the movie?
They talk in English.
They talk in English?
At the point of the movie, nobody can know any language.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
The town's in BC.
It's when people live in caves and stuff like that.
They don't even live in caves.
You don't know.
Maybe they talk English and something.
Maybe they did talk English.
No, no.
I don't think so.
I don't think so, because...
You want to be like Apocalypto?
Yeah.
That they're talking another language and...
Apocalypto's good.
I like that one.
Awesome.
Who was awesome?
Untraceable.
You saw Untraceable already?
Oh, I didn't see him, man.
I missed it.
I think that...
They took it off?
Yeah, they took it off.
It's coming out on DVD then.
I saw the bank job.
You saw it?
It's good.
The bank job's good, yeah.
I want to see it.
I like those things.
I have seen the trailers and it's good.
What about the Hulk, Incredible Hulk?
You saw the trailer?
Yeah.
You saw it?
What do you think?
Good, huh?
But I don't like the guy.
The guy in the movie, I don't like him.
I like him.
I like him better than the other guy.
I'm not a special movie.
I don't like him.
Because that guy is too serious to be on that movie.
You think?
But everyone loves Edward Norton.
I like it how he works.
Yeah.
But...
But it's all...
It's like putting Anthony Hopkins in that movie.
Anthony Hopkins?
Yeah.
You could do it?
Nah, it's an actor.
Look, if you're a good actor, you could do anything.
But you're too serious to watch movies.
Look at The Rock.
The Rock did Saturday Night Live.
The Rock started doing action movies.
Which one was The Rock?
The actor.
The Rock.
Oh.
He does comedy.
You know, Vin Diesel?
Yeah.
He did a comedy?
Yeah, I know.
The pacifier?
No, the only one that I don't like from him is...
How old are you, sir?
Trey is the thing that it is.
Trey, yeah.
Oh, man.
It was like...
Stupid.
Stupid?
You're sorry?
It's the movie?
strays?
Trey's?
You told me it wasn't good.
Don't even look.
They got like a thousand movies on the blockbuster.
Like the same movie?
Uh-huh.
Like a thousand.
Of what?
Of that one?
Yeah.
They got like a thousand.
Just one will for him.
Yesterday I saw Elizabeth, the Golden Age.
I got it at home.
I saw it.
Is it good?
It's good.
Did you see the first one?
No.
No?
I want to see the first one.
Oh, dad.
But they don't got it in Spanish.
My dad doesn't speak English.
You should see the first one.
I mean, you don't have to see the first one to understand the second.
Uh-huh.
But you know, it's good to see the first one.
But it's good.
But part two has like more action.
Part one has no action.
Part two has like some action towards the end.
But if you see part two before part one, when you see part one, I mean, when you see part
two before you see part one, when you see part one, you're going to know something that
happened on part two that you don't want to know?
Uh, no.
Not really.
No?
No.
But see it.
You can see part two and see part one.
Yeah.
And nothing's going to happen.
It's just in part one, they show you like how she becomes the queen.
You know, in part two, she's already the queen.
Yeah.
But they don't have any Spanish subtitles.
Are you sure they're not Spanish?
No, they don't have them.
And you need subtitles because that movie is hard to understand.
But in part two, in England, they're going to war against Spain.
So every time they show Spain, they're talking in Spanish.
On the first one?
On the second one.
The second one?
They talk a lot of Spanish in the second one.
I have seen like part of the movies because I want to say something about what happened
on, you know, like perfume, you saw perfume, right?
Yeah.
I want to see if they had perfume or if it was like that.
Yeah, you know, I think it's more older than perfume.
Like the, the time, it was older than perfume.
Do you work that kind of show?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The guy works there.
Five on.
Have you seen Bad Boys 2?
Yeah.
You know, the bad guy, the bad guy in part two?
The guy in the bad guy.
The guy in the Cuban, the guy with the hair, the bad guy.
El que dice que le va dar un million de pesos a los niños de la casa.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
El es el malo in the Golden Age.
El es de España el malo.
Oh.
El Flaco.
Yeah.
That's when the little girl was like, hey, look at the dress.
And he's like, you're a beautiful one.
His friend last.
And he's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not the one that destroyed the entire Spanish fleet.
What?
Le destruyen toda la flota de España.
Yeah.
Es en esa?
Creo que es la destrucción mas grande que ha tenido espana de la guerra.
Esa no es la que quema la gente viva porque es catolíca.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
They don't show it, but yeah, they talk about it.
Yeah.
Esa clase de película me confunde, pero.
Pero I watch with my girlfriend and she explains what's going on here.
She knows about it.
She's good with that.
I was seeing this, un documentario, de lo que Paso en realidad con this guy, es que adivino el futuro.
We give it to him.
Eso era algo duro.
Elizabeth goes to him to find out what's going to happen in the future.
Elizabeth?
Ella se lo da.
Oh, really?
I don't know if he gave it to him, but he's a prophet.
So he tells him what's going to happen in the future.
El le dice a un rey lo que le va a paaar.
And it actually happens to the king.